sendfromchina.com 2012-05-05

# China Postal Service starts from US$0.95, International Courier Service starts from US$7 - SFC Service Ltd.

### Our commitment to privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected We use this information to process your orders, and communicate with you about the status of your orders. We also use your email address to send you newsletters you subscribe during registration, as well as messages about SFC's special offers, promotional announcements and consumer surveys. 

### The information we collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on SFC website. The type of information we will collect about you includes:

  * Your name
  * Address
  * Phone number
  * Email address
  * The recipient’s contact info.

###  How we use information

Your personal information is directly connected with your transactions. Moreover, we use these information to provide you with personalized services. For example, informing you about new features and other special offers. We also use these information to cater to your needs and requests more efficiently.

  * Cookies. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your computer when you register at our Website. It enables our server to "recognize" or "remember" who you are each time you log in. Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser's help file directions.
  * Log files. Like most standard website servers, we use log files. This includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Sharing-Third parties

We will not disclose your personal information that are related to membership registration or purchases, except with your knowledge and consent as described in this Privacy Policy or as may be required by law, or to protect the rights or property of SFC.

We will not, except as may be required by law, share with any other party your password or payment information. But we may share information about you (including name, email address, phone number, and postal address) to our marketing partners or other companies with whom we have commercial relationship, so that they can contact you about information and services that we feel you would benefit from.

We reserve the right to disclose aggregated user statistics, such as "45% of our users are female" in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties. Under the protection of confidentiality agreements, SFC may match common user information, such as name, address and phone number with third party data to avoid duplication and prevent errors. 

### Our commitment to data security

SFC takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected no matter they are online or off-line.

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our order clerk or customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage in a locked facility.

SFC reserves the right to make any amendments, modifications or changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If any material change is made to this Privacy Policy, we will notify our users about those changes via email. If you do not agree to such changes, you can modify your notification settings to opt out certain notices from SFC or its marketing partners. 

### Contact Us

Any queries, comments or requests you may have regarding this policy. Please do not hesitate to contact us at  <http://www.sendfromchina.com/about.php>
